https://www.tradingeagles.com/trading-eagles-privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Trading Eagles Privacy PolicyMark James2020-08-17T08:03:48-05:00
Trading Eagles Privacy Policy
Through the Trading Eagles Privacy Policy, Tradingeagles.com is committed to protecting your privacy. We have implemented technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. Above all, this Privacy Policy Statement applies to all data collection and data usage in the Tradingeagles.com site. Read the complete privacy statement below to learn about how Tradingeagles.com protects your personal information.
Trading Eagles Privacy Policy and identifiable personal information
Tradingeagles.com collects personally identifiable information, including your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. This information is used  only to provide our services that you request. As such, we do not sell, distribute, or in any other way release your information to any third parties.
The tradingeagles.com website uses “cookies“. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. As a result, Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you. Cookies can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie.
Tradingeagles.com secured your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Therefore, tradingeagles.com secured the access of the personally identifiable information. The information you provided is on a server that is in a controlled, secured environment. Therefore, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Personal information is transmitted to our website and payment processors through a Secure Socket Layer (SSL). The SSL is an encrypted protection. Thus, lour GeoTrust emblem at the bottom of the page. The tradingeagles.com server is PCI Compliant. We do not store any credit card information.
We welcome your comments regarding the Trading Eagles Privacy Policy. Please contact tradingeagles.com by telephone, e-mail, or postal mail and express your concern.
Mark E. James
Tradingeagles.com
920 Leadville Drive
Arlington, Texas 76001
817-797-9146
Product Categories1 - Clearance Memorabilia
1a Consignments
Consignor 1 DF
Unidentified Council Rounds, Patches and Manufacturers Samples
4 - Awards, Recognitions
Belt Loops, Academics pins, Sport pins, Webelos Activity Pins, Skill Awards, related books
Unidentified Council Camp and National Camp Patches and Awrads
Westpoint and Warship weekend camp overs
6 - Jamborees: National Jamborees, National Scout Jamborees, US Contingent and World Jamborees, Moots, Modials, Regional
1920 - Date US Contingent World Jamborees
1920 - Date World Jamborees, World Memorabilia, World Modials, Moots, Regional Jamborees
Adult Professional Positions at the Council District and National Levels
Shirts, Pants, Shoulder Loops, Belts, Buckles, Spats, Socks, Garters
Unit Specific Uniform Parts, Patches
9A - International Scouting
Boy Scout and Girl Guides Rank, Participation Awards, Patches, Pins, Jewelry, Other International Memorabilia
International Scout Literature, Resources, Books, Decals, Media
9B - Girl Scout Memorabilia
GSA Patches, GSA Pins
Uniforms, Uniform Parts
Unit, Personal Equipment, Additional Unit Memorabilia, Additional Personal Memorabilia
